[
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, where is the nearest gas station?\"\n\n&#x200B;\n\n\"Okay so you're going to want to drive past that building that used to be the old dentist office. Take a right at the large yellow house.  Keep going until you see that sign for the restaurant we went to last year and then take a left.  If you've reached the place where Time Hortons used to be, then you've gone too far\"",
    "score": 47609,
    "author": "mpizzle3",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8njn17/",
    "question": "Where is the nearest gas station?",
    "answer": "&#x200B;\nOkay so you're going to want to drive past that building that used to be the old dentist office. Take a right at the large yellow house.  Keep going until you see that sign for the restaurant we went to last year and then take a left.  If you've reached the place where Time Hortons used to be, then you've gone too far"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, open YouTube.\"\n\n\"How? Can you show me?\"",
    "score": 39503,
    "author": "gottamemethemall",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqgl1/",
    "question": "Open youtube.",
    "answer": "How? Can you show me?"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok Boomer, what's the weather like?\n\n\"Why don't you go for a walk and see for yourself?\"",
    "score": 38996,
    "author": "Savageschool13",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nksnf/",
    "question": "What's the weather like?",
    "answer": "Why don't you go for a walk and see for yourself?"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok Boomer, play today\u2019s hits. \n\nTHAT is NOT music!",
    "score": 30627,
    "author": "onesillymom",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnssc/",
    "question": "Play today\u2019s hits.",
    "answer": "THAT is NOT music!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK Boomer, Call my Husband\u201d\n\n\u201cOnly if you tell me when I\u2019m going to get grandkids!!! It\u2019s about time!\u201d",
    "score": 27152,
    "author": "Chaosncalculation",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8noq0d/",
    "question": "Call my husband",
    "answer": "Only if you tell me when I\u2019m going to get grandkids!!! It\u2019s about time!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, how's the weather today?\"\n\n\n\"Alexa?\"\n\n\n\"No, you're supposed to answer me\"\n\n\n\"Alexa are you listening? I can't tell if it's listening. Do I start talking yet? I think it stopped. Directions to this address....Alexa?\"",
    "score": 23808,
    "author": "ScooterMcThumbkin",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnxit/",
    "question": "How's the weather today?",
    "answer": "Alexa?\nNo, you're supposed to answer me\nAlexa are you listening? I can't tell if it's listening. Do I start talking yet? I think it stopped. Directions to this address....Alexa?"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, restaurants near by\"\n\n\"we have food at home\"",
    "score": 22202,
    "author": "WaluigisOveralls",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8njcxu/",
    "question": "Restaurants near by",
    "answer": "we have food at home"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, Engineering job listings in my area.\"\n\n\"Job listings? You are just playing around on the internet. Figure out where you want to work and go down there. Ask to speak with a manager. Shake his hand, look him in the eye and ask for a job!\"\n\nEdit: This post brought to you by painful memories of job hunting during the 2008 recession. My dad was getting on my case every day about \"playing on the computer\" when I was checking job sites and going through their infuriating sites that make me upload my resume, then fill in fields that are on my resume three different times. Someone in the comments below dropped the classic \"Pound the pavement\" and I felt my blood pressure spike. Thanks.",
    "score": 20618,
    "author": "Wyvrex",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nz5mk/",
    "question": "Engineering job listings in my area.",
    "answer": " This post brought to you by painful memories of job hunting during the 2008 recession. My dad was getting on my case every day about playing on the computer when I was checking job sites and going through their infuriating sites that make me upload my resume, then fill in fields that are on my resume three different times. Someone in the comments below dropped the classic Pound the pavement and I felt my blood pressure spike. Thanks."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK Boomer, how's the weather today?\n\n\"Open the window and stick your arm out. Is it wet? That must mean it's raining. Is it cold? Put on a sweater. Try figuring out things on your own kiddo.\"",
    "score": 20006,
    "author": "PM_ME_UR_FAVE-SHIRT",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nm1z9/",
    "question": "How's the weather today?",
    "answer": "Open the window and stick your arm out. Is it wet? That must mean it's raining. Is it cold? Put on a sweater. Try figuring out things on your own kiddo."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk boomer, how can I pay for college?\u201d\n\n\u201cWrite a check like I did!\u201d",
    "score": 17090,
    "author": "riiptemp",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nm5ka/",
    "question": "How can i pay for college?",
    "answer": "Write a check like I did!"
  },
  {
    "body": "OK Boomer look up therapists near me\n\nHave you tried thinking positive thoughts?",
    "score": 17028,
    "author": "howiejriii",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nn2sm/",
    "question": "Look up therapists near me",
    "answer": "Have you tried thinking positive thoughts?"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, what time is it?''\n\n\"What? You don't know how to read a clock? The future is doomed.\"",
    "score": 15855,
    "author": "ousteT",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nk5pc/",
    "question": "What time is it?''",
    "answer": "What? You don't know how to read a clock? The future is doomed."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, directions to 5th and Montgomery.\"\n\n\"we don't need a map, I know where it is.\"\n\n*waits a minute*\n\n\"...uh...\"",
    "score": 15039,
    "author": "Voittaa",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8no27v/",
    "question": "Directions to 5th and montgomery.",
    "answer": "we don't need a map, I know where it is.\n*waits a minute*\n...uh..."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK boomer, turn the thermostat to 23\u00b0C.\n\nThat function is locked to users.",
    "score": 14249,
    "author": "smileedude",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nna1u/",
    "question": "Turn the thermostat to 23\u00b0c.",
    "answer": "That function is locked to users."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK Boo\u2014\u201c\n\n\u201cBy your age I had a house, car, and 50k in savings. You need to stop asking for handouts\u201d",
    "score": 12428,
    "author": "tarahdactyl_x",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8no722/",
    "question": "OK Boo\u2014",
    "answer": "By your age I had a house, car, and 50k in savings. You need to stop asking for handouts"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, what's the most effective birth control pill?\"\n\n*\"The most effective birth control pill is an aspirin between your knees.\"*\n\n\n[Actual quote from a friend's parent, I'll never forget it.]",
    "score": 12274,
    "author": "ninaruminatti",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nrug1/",
    "question": "What's the most effective birth control pill?",
    "answer": "*The most effective birth control pill is an aspirin between your knees.*\n[Actual quote from a friend's parent, I'll never forget it.]"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, take me to the nearest formal sit-down place\"\n\n\"Ok snowflake, starting your route to Applebee's\"",
    "score": 9639,
    "author": "EBandD123",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nmdab/",
    "question": "Take me to the nearest formal sit-down place",
    "answer": "Ok snowflake, starting your route to Applebee's"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, what's the capital of Iraq?\"\n\n\"Back in my day, we looked things up in an encyclopedia. Damn millennials, so obsessed with their phones.\"",
    "score": 8610,
    "author": "ostentia",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nma7a/",
    "question": "What's the capital of iraq?",
    "answer": "Back in my day, we looked things up in an encyclopedia. Damn millennials, so obsessed with their phones."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, what's on TV right now?\"\n\n\"We only watch the news and Wheel of Fortune in this house.\"",
    "score": 7244,
    "author": "Pantelima",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8npici/",
    "question": "What's on tv right now?",
    "answer": "We only watch the news and Wheel of Fortune in this house."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, tell me a joke\"\n\n\"You snowflakes get offended over eveything. You can't even take a joke\"\n\n\"Ok boomer\"\n\n\"What did you say you little shit?\"",
    "score": 7183,
    "author": "_fetaljuice",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnv9v/",
    "question": "Tell me a joke",
    "answer": "You snowflakes get offended over eveything. You can't even take a joke\nOk boomer\nWhat did you say you little shit?"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok Boomer; what restaurants serve brunch near me?\n\n\"Have you tried not being gay?\"",
    "score": 6036,
    "author": "Claim_to_Lame",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nkut5/",
    "question": "What restaurants serve brunch near me?",
    "answer": "Have you tried not being gay?"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, where's the nearest recycling center.\"\n\n\"We have trash cans.\"",
    "score": 4964,
    "author": "beatboxingfox",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nre8t/",
    "question": "Where's the nearest recycling center.",
    "answer": "We have trash cans."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK Boomer, where\u2019s the nearest car mechanic?\u201d\n\n\u201cWhat, you can\u2019t fix your car yourself? Kids these days.\u201d\n\n\u201c...Boomer, my engine literally just exploded...\u201d\n\n\u201cI\u2019m sorry, I can\u2019t hear you. Try not mumbling. *E-nun-ci-ate, your, words.*\u201d\n\n\u201cErm, right. OK Boomer, what\u2019s the number for my insurance company?\u201d\n\n\u201cYou don\u2019t have it memorized?! Sad. Where would you be without your smartphones and iTablet thingies?\u201d\n\n\u201c...you know what, never mind, I\u2019ll just walk. Thanks, Boomer.\u201d\n\n\u201cWalking, finally, a *good* idea. Exercise. You\u2019re all so chubby. Don\u2019t eat right with all that Chipotle Bell stuff. And it\u2019s *thank you*, not \u2018thanks.\u2019 And my response is \u2018you\u2019re welcome,\u2019 not that ridiculous \u2018no problem\u2019 you all do.\u201d\n\n\u201c.....OK Boomer, please stop now.\u201d\n\n\u201cDon\u2019t you tell me to be quiet! Have some respect for your elders! When I was your age I owned a house!\u201d",
    "score": 4087,
    "author": "MagicalMonarchOfMo",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8np8as/",
    "question": "Where\u2019s the nearest car mechanic?",
    "answer": "What, you can\u2019t fix your car yourself? Kids these days.\n...Boomer, my engine literally just exploded...\nI\u2019m sorry, I can\u2019t hear you. Try not mumbling. *E-nun-ci-ate, your, words.*\nErm, right. OK Boomer, what\u2019s the number for my insurance company?\nYou don\u2019t have it memorized?! Sad. Where would you be without your smartphones and iTablet thingies?\n...you know what, never mind, I\u2019ll just walk. Thanks, Boomer.\nWalking, finally, a *good* idea. Exercise. You\u2019re all so chubby. Don\u2019t eat right with all that Chipotle Bell stuff. And it\u2019s *thank you*, not \u2018thanks.\u2019 And my response is \u2018you\u2019re welcome,\u2019 not that ridiculous \u2018no problem\u2019 you all do.\n.....OK Boomer, please stop now.\nDon\u2019t you tell me to be quiet! Have some respect for your elders! When I was your age I owned a house!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, open Indeed!\"\n\n\"You don't need Indeed! Just walk on in and give a firm handshake you entitled brat. And while you're at it, you can send out resumes in the mail. I bet you don't even know what stamps are you avocado-toast-eating millennial!\"",
    "score": 3859,
    "author": "Commander_Shepard_",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nlcqe/",
    "question": "Open indeed!",
    "answer": "You don't need Indeed! Just walk on in and give a firm handshake you entitled brat. And while you're at it, you can send out resumes in the mail. I bet you don't even know what stamps are you avocado-toast-eating millennial!"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer, the job market is so competitive. How can I get a job?\n\nYa just need gumption! (Proceeds to talk about how they got a job from just walking in and demanding it)",
    "score": 2353,
    "author": "gaberoman",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nm249/",
    "question": "The job market is so competitive. how can i get a job?",
    "answer": "Ya just need gumption! (Proceeds to talk about how they got a job from just walking in and demanding it)"
  },
  {
    "body": "You: \"OK Boomer, what are the local showtimes for Avengers?\"\n\nDigital Assistant: \"I can't figure me out, you have to show me how to work myself, why am I so slow?\"\n\nYou: \"Goddamnit stop running all those malware programs.\"",
    "score": 2230,
    "author": "pm_me_your_molars",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nm1ig/",
    "question": "What are the local showtimes for avengers?",
    "answer": "Digital Assistant: I can't figure me out, you have to show me how to work myself, why am I so slow?\nYou: Goddamnit stop running all those malware programs."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK boomer, volume up\"\n\n\"What, you wanna become deaf?\"",
    "score": 1573,
    "author": "Hq3473",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nng02/",
    "question": "Volume up",
    "answer": "What, you wanna become deaf?"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok Boomer, can you please auto-fill my credit card details on this site ?\n\nWhat, you want to give your details to a stranger ? Are you nuts ? Just go drive a half an hour to the store and buy it in person, it's safer that way.",
    "score": 1548,
    "author": "nagynorbie",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8noorg/",
    "question": "Can you please auto-fill my credit card details on this site ?",
    "answer": "What, you want to give your details to a stranger ? Are you nuts ? Just go drive a half an hour to the store and buy it in person, it's safer that way."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, set my alarm for 9:00 AM tomorrow.\"\n\n\"9:00? Are you sure? I see in your calendar that your flight boards at 10:30 and taking into account how it takes 30 minutes to get to the airport, that only leaves you with 1 hour to make it to your gate in time. Why don't I set your alarm for 5:00 AM instead? Or maybe 6:00, if you really want to sleep in?\"",
    "score": 1538,
    "author": "anyahwtf",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nkawi/",
    "question": "Set my alarm for 9:00 am tomorrow.",
    "answer": "9:00? Are you sure? I see in your calendar that your flight boards at 10:30 and taking into account how it takes 30 minutes to get to the airport, that only leaves you with 1 hour to make it to your gate in time. Why don't I set your alarm for 5:00 AM instead? Or maybe 6:00, if you really want to sleep in?"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, what should I wear today\u201d   THE WHITE NEW BALANCES!  ALWAYS THE WHITE NEW BALANCES!",
    "score": 1484,
    "author": "slayalldayyyy",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nn9zt/",
    "question": "What should i wear today",
    "answer": " THE WHITE NEW BALANCES!\nALWAYS THE WHITE NEW BALANCES!"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok Boomer: remind me to take my medication \n\nYou don\u2019t need that stuff! Just snap out of it!",
    "score": 1029,
    "author": "donteatmee3333",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqarn/",
    "question": "Remind me to take my medication",
    "answer": "You don\u2019t need that stuff! Just snap out of it!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Figure it out for yourself\" and \"Do it yourself\"\n\n&#x200B;\n\nwould be the only lines of dialogue on the chip.",
    "score": 970,
    "author": "TheFlemishBlemish",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nltxb/",
    "question": "...",
    "answer": "Figure it out for yourself and Do it yourself\nwould be the only lines of dialogue on the chip."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, do I need to go to college?\u201d\n\n\u201cHell no, just get a job at a factory and buy a house right out of high school!\u201d",
    "score": 897,
    "author": "Bionicjoker",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nj844/",
    "question": "Do i need to go to college?",
    "answer": "Hell no, just get a job at a factory and buy a house right out of high school!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK Boomer, open my mail messages\u201d \n\n\u201cI\u2019m sorry, there\u2019s no mail delivery on Sundays.\u201d",
    "score": 784,
    "author": "Laymans_Terms19",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8np8jt/",
    "question": "Open my mail messages",
    "answer": "I\u2019m sorry, there\u2019s no mail delivery on Sundays."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, tell me about how life was so easy in your time\"\n\n\"I had a part time job moving boxes and I could support a stay at home wife, 3 kids, 2 dogs, a cat, a car, and what is basically a mansion in today's world. I don't get why you always complain that life is so hard\"",
    "score": 703,
    "author": "Ricky_RZ",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8no82k/",
    "question": "Tell me about how life was so easy in your time",
    "answer": "I had a part time job moving boxes and I could support a stay at home wife, 3 kids, 2 dogs, a cat, a car, and what is basically a mansion in today's world. I don't get why you always complain that life is so hard"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, show me job application links\"\n\"Here are the addresses of nearby offices with job listings. Their office hours are 9-5, so show up at 8:30 and expect an interview.\"",
    "score": 625,
    "author": "Whenitrainsitpours86",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8npaak/",
    "question": "Show me job application links",
    "answer": "Here are the addresses of nearby offices with job listings. Their office hours are 9-5, so show up at 8:30 and expect an interview."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, how do I fix my crushing debt\"\n\n\"ORDERING. ONE PAIR. BOOTSTRAPS.\"",
    "score": 570,
    "author": "moronicuniform",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq92g/",
    "question": "How do i fix my crushing debt",
    "answer": "ORDERING. ONE PAIR. BOOTSTRAPS."
  },
  {
    "body": "How do I get rid of student loans? \n\nWork hard, stop being lazy and useless all the time. I used to work 40 hours a day in the fields",
    "score": 558,
    "author": "YeetVegetabales",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nl6g4/",
    "question": "How do I get rid of student loans? ",
    "answer": "Work hard, stop being lazy and useless all the time. I used to work 40 hours a day in the fields"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, which radio station should I listen to?\u201d \n\n\u201cDoesn\u2019t matter, music nowadays is all trash\u201d",
    "score": 490,
    "author": "losersftw",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnje6/",
    "question": "Which radio station should i listen to?",
    "answer": "Doesn\u2019t matter, music nowadays is all trash"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, how should I ask her out?\"\n\nBoomer: \"Back in my day, we didn't ask\"",
    "score": 411,
    "author": "bigsalad98",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq0vc/",
    "question": "How should i ask her out?",
    "answer": "Boomer: Back in my day, we didn't ask"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"how can I afford college?\"\n\"Get a higher paying job\"\n\"How can I get a raise?\"\n\"Get a degree\"",
    "score": 396,
    "author": "bearofcholes",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8np5sy/",
    "question": "how can I afford college?",
    "answer": "Get a higher paying job\nHow can I get a raise?\nGet a degree"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, where is the nearest park\"\n\n\n\n\"When I was your age me and your grandmother would walk to Wilson park and have malts\"",
    "score": 301,
    "author": "Roc_City",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnpoy/",
    "question": "Where is the nearest park",
    "answer": "When I was your age me and your grandmother would walk to Wilson park and have malts"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, h-\"\n\n#**\"IT'S PAST 9 PM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING AWAKE? THIS GENERATION CAN'T GO A MINUTE WITHOUT USING THEIR DAMN PHONES.\"**",
    "score": 278,
    "author": "windwaker3656",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nrh4p/",
    "question": "H-",
    "answer": "#**IT'S PAST 9 PM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING AWAKE? THIS GENERATION CAN'T GO A MINUTE WITHOUT USING THEIR DAMN PHONES.**"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, what does [insert word] mean?\"\n\n\"Oh my god get a dictionary and get off your phone. Go into the real world and maybe get a job. God, this generation is doomed.\" \n(Probably longer but I'm too lazy to type)",
    "score": 272,
    "author": "trixabellian_Quartz",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnhp8/",
    "question": "What does [insert word] mean?",
    "answer": "Oh my god get a dictionary and get off your phone. Go into the real world and maybe get a job. God, this generation is doomed. \n(Probably longer but I'm too lazy to type)"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, start my PC.\"\n\n\nBoomer: \"I told you I'm not a computer person! You're not helping me so I'm hanging up now. Goodbye!\"",
    "score": 248,
    "author": "LonelyPauper",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nr6sm/",
    "question": "Start my pc.",
    "answer": "Boomer: I told you I'm not a computer person! You're not helping me so I'm hanging up now. Goodbye!"
  },
  {
    "body": "*Turns on phone*\n\n\"On your phone? Again? Kids these days, always got their eyes glued to a screen.\"",
    "score": 220,
    "author": "FalafelsOnWaffles",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq2jy/",
    "question": "*Turns on phone*",
    "answer": "On your phone? Again? Kids these days, always got their eyes glued to a screen."
  },
  {
    "body": "How do yo retire comfortably boomer?\n\nYou graduate high school, get a job with a large company, buy a house by 25, work for 45 years, get retirement with a paid off house.",
    "score": 216,
    "author": "gaff2049",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq12h/",
    "question": "?",
    "answer": "You graduate high school, get a job with a large company, buy a house by 25, work for 45 years, get retirement with a paid off house."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer. Which candidate should I vote for?\"\n\n\"Searching for sexual criminals in your county.\"",
    "score": 179,
    "author": "DirtyPrancin",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nrzdc/",
    "question": "Which candidate should i vote for?",
    "answer": "Searching for sexual criminals in your county."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK Boomer, what\u2019s the news today?\n\n\u201cI saw on Facebook that the liberals are....\u201d",
    "score": 164,
    "author": "pol_pots",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nskw2/",
    "question": "What\u2019s the news today?",
    "answer": "I saw on Facebook that the liberals are...."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, give me a recipe for apple pie\"\n\n\"Get in your car, drive 4 blocks down main street until you arrive at the library. Ask the librarian for a recipe book.\"",
    "score": 159,
    "author": "DeathSpiral321",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8npha1/",
    "question": "Give me a recipe for apple pie",
    "answer": "Get in your car, drive 4 blocks down main street until you arrive at the library. Ask the librarian for a recipe book."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, what restaurants are around me?\"\n\n\"THERE IS AN OLIVE GARDEN AND AN APPLEBEE'S 5 MILES AWAy FrOM WheReE YOU ARE NOW PERIOD NO STOP DON'T TYPE THAT YOU STUPID PHONE. THAT OLIVE GARDEN SAYS THAT IT OFFERS UNLIMITED BREADSTICKS BUT THEY CUT ME OFF AFTER SIX BOWLS AND TOLD ME THAT I HAD TO chooSE SOMETHING FROM THe MENu. THE WAITER WASN'T FILLING OUR DRINKS FAST ENOUGH EITHER, SO I SNAPPED MY FINGERS AT HIM TO GET HIS ATTENTION. HE DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE. THERE GOES HIS TIP!!! ANYWAY, I HOPE YOU ARE DOING ALRIGHT. YOUR UNCLE IS IN THE HOSPITAL AGAIN. THEY SAY HE's NOT LOOKING TOO GOOD. YOU SHOULD VISIT HIM. IT MIGHT BE THE LAST TIME YOU SEE HIM BEFORE HE DIES PERIOD NO TYPE A PERIOD AND SEND--\"",
    "score": 144,
    "author": "cricketjacked",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nypce/",
    "question": "What restaurants are around me?",
    "answer": "THERE IS AN OLIVE GARDEN AND AN APPLEBEE'S 5 MILES AWAy FrOM WheReE YOU ARE NOW PERIOD NO STOP DON'T TYPE THAT YOU STUPID PHONE. THAT OLIVE GARDEN SAYS THAT IT OFFERS UNLIMITED BREADSTICKS BUT THEY CUT ME OFF AFTER SIX BOWLS AND TOLD ME THAT I HAD TO chooSE SOMETHING FROM THe MENu. THE WAITER WASN'T FILLING OUR DRINKS FAST ENOUGH EITHER, SO I SNAPPED MY FINGERS AT HIM TO GET HIS ATTENTION. HE DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE. THERE GOES HIS TIP!!! ANYWAY, I HOPE YOU ARE DOING ALRIGHT. YOUR UNCLE IS IN THE HOSPITAL AGAIN. THEY SAY HE's NOT LOOKING TOO GOOD. YOU SHOULD VISIT HIM. IT MIGHT BE THE LAST TIME YOU SEE HIM BEFORE HE DIES PERIOD NO TYPE A PERIOD AND SEND--"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cQuit being a bitch and work harder, no one is going to give you shit.\u201d \n\n- works for all questions with ok boomer",
    "score": 131,
    "author": "grab_ur_rape_whistle",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nj11q/",
    "question": "Quit being a bitch and work harder, no one is going to give you shit. ",
    "answer": "- works for all questions with ok boomer"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, when is International Women's Day?\"\n\n\"What about International Men's Day? When's that eh?\"",
    "score": 112,
    "author": "TheColdThought",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8np7dq/",
    "question": "When is international women's day?",
    "answer": "What about International Men's Day? When's that eh?"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer, take me to this address in the Loop.  \n\nYou don't want to go there it's a bad neighbor you'll get shoy.",
    "score": 100,
    "author": "Rabidleopard",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nogex/",
    "question": "Take me to this address in the loop.",
    "answer": "You don't want to go there it's a bad neighbor you'll get shoy."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK Boomer, wake me up at 6:00\n\n*wakes you up at 5:00*\n\n\u201cGet up, its 6:00!!!\u201d",
    "score": 97,
    "author": "MrMager",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o3dlj/",
    "question": "Wake me up at 6:00",
    "answer": "*wakes you up at 5:00*\nGet up, its 6:00!!!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, how do I apply for a job?\"\n\n\"You walk into the place you want to work at with your resume printed out, ask for an application. Then you sit down, fill it out, and hand it in!  \nThen you ask to speak to their boss so you can shake their hand.\"",
    "score": 97,
    "author": "mycological-amatoxin",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nujv9/",
    "question": "How do i apply for a job?",
    "answer": "You walk into the place you want to work at with your resume printed out, ask for an application. Then you sit down, fill it out, and hand it in!  \nThen you ask to speak to their boss so you can shake their hand."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, why are you racist\"\n\n\"I'm not racist, I have a black friend\"",
    "score": 96,
    "author": "ThisisSeen",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8npszq/",
    "question": "Why are you racist",
    "answer": "I'm not racist, I have a black friend"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, what\u2019s the weather like today?\u201d\n\n\u201cIt\u2019s very chilly today. That means climate change is a hoax.\u201d",
    "score": 89,
    "author": "FreeSkeptic",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o111g/",
    "question": "What\u2019s the weather like today?",
    "answer": "It\u2019s very chilly today. That means climate change is a hoax."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, where's the nearest club?\"\n\n\"There's no way you're going out looking like that\"",
    "score": 76,
    "author": "OneSalientOversight",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8np8tl/",
    "question": "Where's the nearest club?",
    "answer": "There's no way you're going out looking like that"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Okay, Boomer.  Please help me find the closest oil change service\"  \n\n\n\"You seriously are going to pay for an oil change? Did your dad  not teach you to be a man? Anyways, what you want to do is go to the nearest local Auto Parts store. You need to figure out what oil you need in the manual that's in your glove box. Generally, 5W-30 is a safe bet. Now you wanna find a good filter. Don't ask the clerk, just use the book that's by the filters and find what you need. Anyways, just take it back to the garage and change it yourself. There, I saved you $30 from that overpriced service.\"",
    "score": 69,
    "author": "Kyhunsheo",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o0c2i/",
    "question": "Please help me find the closest oil change service",
    "answer": "You seriously are going to pay for an oil change? Did your dad  not teach you to be a man? Anyways, what you want to do is go to the nearest local Auto Parts store. You need to figure out what oil you need in the manual that's in your glove box. Generally, 5W-30 is a safe bet. Now you wanna find a good filter. Don't ask the clerk, just use the book that's by the filters and find what you need. Anyways, just take it back to the garage and change it yourself. There, I saved you $30 from that overpriced service."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK Boomer, what's the recipe for vegan paleo power-boost pancakes with chia- and flax-seed, and beetroot dressing?\n\nBoomer: \"GraaaghlghlghahrghgRAAAAAAGHLGGHHHHGNNNN!!!!!!!\"",
    "score": 65,
    "author": "Jervillian_Swike",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nrtou/",
    "question": "What's the recipe for vegan paleo power-boost pancakes with chia- and flax-seed, and beetroot dressing?",
    "answer": "Boomer: GraaaghlghlghahrghgRAAAAAAGHLGGHHHHGNNNN!!!!!!!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, how do I get to Starbucks?\u201d\n\n*\u201cWhat, to get one of your vegan organic caramel vanilla millennial frappuccinos?\u201d*\n\n\u201cJust tell me how to get there\u201d\n\n*\u201cJust use a roadmap like everyone else\u201d*\n\n(mumbling under breath) \u201cYeah, like everyone else over 60\u201d\n\n*\u201dWhat was that?\u201d*\n\n\u201cI said... Ok boomer, call Starbucks\u201d\n\n*\u201cWhy? Don\u2019t know how to use a phone book?\u201d*\n\n\u201cWhy would I need to know that when I have a digital assistant?\u201d\n\n*\u201dUgh, you millennials think your so entitled to \u2018digital assistants\u2019\u201d*",
    "score": 63,
    "author": "TeboeCubes",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqky9/",
    "question": "How do i get to starbucks?",
    "answer": "*What, to get one of your vegan organic caramel vanilla millennial frappuccinos?*\nJust tell me how to get there\n*Just use a roadmap like everyone else*\n(mumbling under breath) Yeah, like everyone else over 60\n*What was that?*\nI said... Ok boomer, call Starbucks\n*Why? Don\u2019t know how to use a phone book?*\nWhy would I need to know that when I have a digital assistant?\n*Ugh, you millennials think your so entitled to \u2018digital assistants\u2019*"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK, Boomer. Call Jessica from work.\"\n\n\"Who's Jessica? Do you have a girlfriend I don't know about?\"\n\n\"It's not like that and it would be super weird if--\"\n\n\"In my day I'd squeeze her fanny to show I'm interested.\"\n\n\"That's incredibly inappropriate. Can you just--?\"\n\n\"Call history shows you haven't called your grandma in a while.\"\n\n\"Yeah, but she just drones on for h--\"\n\n\"Calling grandma...\"",
    "score": 61,
    "author": "actualspaceturtle",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o2270/",
    "question": "Call jessica from work.",
    "answer": "Who's Jessica? Do you have a girlfriend I don't know about?\nIt's not like that and it would be super weird if--\nIn my day I'd squeeze her fanny to show I'm interested.\nThat's incredibly inappropriate. Can you just--?\nCall history shows you haven't called your grandma in a while.\nYeah, but she just drones on for h--\nCalling grandma..."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer play Despacito\u201d\n\n*Phone dials INS*",
    "score": 61,
    "author": "Allthemedals",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnl1a/",
    "question": "Play despacito",
    "answer": "*Phone dials INS*"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer, how are the 49ers doing?\n\nNot sure but Joe Montana is 10x better than Tom Brady",
    "score": 55,
    "author": "Magnum3k",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nmigt/",
    "question": "How are the 49ers doing?",
    "answer": "Not sure but Joe Montana is 10x better than Tom Brady"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, play music.\u201d   STEELY DAN INTENSIFIES",
    "score": 55,
    "author": "slayalldayyyy",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nlush/",
    "question": "Play music.",
    "answer": " STEELY DAN INTENSIFIES"
  },
  {
    "body": "Me: \"Ok Boomer, directions to disneyland.\"\n\nPhone: \"GPS? Ok is that the one with a G on it?\" \n\nMe: \"No that's google. It's the one that says maps.\"\n\nPhone: \"Hold on let me put my glasses on. Why do they have to put it in such tiny letters? I'm just gonna turn the music down so I can see. Ah here it is. Now where did you want to go? Disneyland? Is that the one in Florida or California? You know when I was a kid me and my entire family went to Disney out in California and...(continues on anecdote)\"\n\nMe: \"Fuck it I'll do it myself!\"",
    "score": 53,
    "author": "YoderMcLongDong",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o1es3/",
    "question": "Directions to disneyland.",
    "answer": "Phone: GPS? Ok is that the one with a G on it? \nMe: No that's google. It's the one that says maps.\nPhone: Hold on let me put my glasses on. Why do they have to put it in such tiny letters? I'm just gonna turn the music down so I can see. Ah here it is. Now where did you want to go? Disneyland? Is that the one in Florida or California? You know when I was a kid me and my entire family went to Disney out in California and...(continues on anecdote)\nMe: Fuck it I'll do it myself!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Okay Boomer, how will the world end?\"\n\n\"You millenials fucked it up, *you guys* are the reason we're gonna die! And don't try arguing with me! Your guys's generation can't even decide if its a boy or girl!\"",
    "score": 48,
    "author": "_-Tsunami-_",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o2mtc/",
    "question": "How will the world end?",
    "answer": "You millenials fucked it up, *you guys* are the reason we're gonna die! And don't try arguing with me! Your guys's generation can't even decide if its a boy or girl!"
  },
  {
    "body": "'OK Boomer, tell me a joke'\n\n'A Jew, a Mexican, and a Black Muslim walk into a ... '\n\nIm gona stop because Im not a boomer. My dad wont stop with this shit",
    "score": 45,
    "author": "topcheesehead",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8ntgco/",
    "question": "Tell me a joke'",
    "answer": "'A Jew, a Mexican, and a Black Muslim walk into a ... '\nIm gona stop because Im not a boomer. My dad wont stop with this shit"
  },
  {
    "body": "Being late Gen X, I\u2019ve seen all this before back when the boomers said it to the Greatest Generation, and when Gen X said it to Boomers.\n\nI hope I don\u2019t die young. I want to see all the Millennials sellout and get picked on for being crabby old doofuses by Generation Whatever.\n\nThe more things change, the more they stay the same.",
    "score": 40,
    "author": "927comewhatmay",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nsv4i/",
    "question": "S said it to the greatest generation, and when gen x said it to boomers.",
    "answer": "I hope I don\u2019t die young. I want to see all the Millennials sellout and get picked on for being crabby old doofuses by Generation Whatever.\nThe more things change, the more they stay the same."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, how do I find a job\"\n\nGo down and talk to the foreman and have a job that you can raise a family on and you retire from in 30yrs with full pension and benefits.",
    "score": 38,
    "author": "ChuckChuckMoeMuck",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nrxac/",
    "question": "How do i find a job",
    "answer": "Go down and talk to the foreman and have a job that you can raise a family on and you retire from in 30yrs with full pension and benefits."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK Boomer, what\u2019s my commute like for today?\u201d\n\u201cEnough with the questions, it\u2019s my turn. *cough/clearthroat* OK Millennial, how do I open the internet?\u201d",
    "score": 38,
    "author": "jstanotherthrwawyl0l",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nv1m6/",
    "question": "What\u2019s my commute like for today?",
    "answer": "Enough with the questions, it\u2019s my turn. *cough/clearthroat* OK Millennial, how do I open the internet?"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer, what time is it?\n\n\u201cYou damm kids are too lazy to wear a watch. What does the little hand say? You don\u2019t know lol\u201d",
    "score": 35,
    "author": "CabinKaiser69",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nmmj2/",
    "question": "What time is it?",
    "answer": "You damm kids are too lazy to wear a watch. What does the little hand say? You don\u2019t know lol"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, find therapists nearby\"\n\n\"Therapist?  You goddamn millennials and your need for therapy. You know what I do when I'm feeling emotional, snowflake? I just bottle it up and drink. Therapists are a waste of money.\"",
    "score": 34,
    "author": "katrinaforaday",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nx9lp/",
    "question": "Find therapists nearby",
    "answer": "Therapist?  You goddamn millennials and your need for therapy. You know what I do when I'm feeling emotional, snowflake? I just bottle it up and drink. Therapists are a waste of money."
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok, boomer where\u2019s the nearest hospital?\n\nYou can\u2019t look at a map?\n\nI AM DYING\n\nYou never deserved to live",
    "score": 31,
    "author": "poplk7",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqs0x/",
    "question": "Where\u2019s the nearest hospital?",
    "answer": "You can\u2019t look at a map?\nI AM DYING\nYou never deserved to live"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, give me information about the global warming\" \n\"Global warming is fake\"",
    "score": 31,
    "author": "Somenerdyfag",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8njrak/",
    "question": "Give me information about the global warming",
    "answer": "Global warming is fake"
  },
  {
    "body": "Me: \"OK Boomer, how's the weather today?\"\n\nOKB: \"Doesn't matter, you're not leaving the house today because you are both too preoccupied with staring at your phone and too lazy to get a job.\"\n\nMe: \"Dude, just tell me the freaking temperature.\"\n\nOKB: \"25 degrees. Where's your precious global warming now?\"\n\nMe: \"Fuck you, climate change has been scientifically proven to be real.\"\n\nOKB: \"Yeah, about as real as all the genders you stupid kids keep making up.\"\n\nMe: \"If you were real I'd put you in a nursing home.\"\n\nOKB: \"At least I could afford a home.\"\n\nMe: *drops phone into garbage disposal*",
    "score": 30,
    "author": "supahfligh",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o4sej/",
    "question": "How's the weather today?",
    "answer": "OKB: Doesn't matter, you're not leaving the house today because you are both too preoccupied with staring at your phone and too lazy to get a job.\nMe: Dude, just tell me the freaking temperature.\nOKB: 25 degrees. Where's your precious global warming now?\nMe: Fuck you, climate change has been scientifically proven to be real.\nOKB: Yeah, about as real as all the genders you stupid kids keep making up.\nMe: If you were real I'd put you in a nursing home.\nOKB: At least I could afford a home.\nMe: *drops phone into garbage disposal*"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOkay Boomer what\u2019s the status of my job applications?\u201d\n\nHave you tried going in there and speaking with the boss?",
    "score": 29,
    "author": "Archibald_Meatpants_",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o3mz2/",
    "question": "What\u2019s the status of my job applications?",
    "answer": "Have you tried going in there and speaking with the boss?"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer, what's the best way of saving for a house deposit?\"\n\n\"Jesus. You kids today are idiots. Stop spending your damned money on Avocado's and Coffee you Moron.\"",
    "score": 27,
    "author": "Captain_Chaos007",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq7gw/",
    "question": "What's the best way of saving for a house deposit?",
    "answer": "Jesus. You kids today are idiots. Stop spending your damned money on Avocado's and Coffee you Moron."
  },
  {
    "body": "Any variation of \"Ok Boomer, should I buy a Big Green Egg?\"\n\nwould always get a yes",
    "score": 26,
    "author": "Gruv_3",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nmr3q/",
    "question": "Should i buy a big green egg?",
    "answer": "would always get a yes"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk boomer, what\u2019s the closest route to my school?\u201d\n\n\u201cWhat, don\u2019t you damn millennials know how to read a map? Back in my day we walked uphill to school both ways in the snow!\u201d\n\n\nAlso, Jacksfilms.",
    "score": 25,
    "author": "Pegg_Legg",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqceq/",
    "question": "What\u2019s the closest route to my school?",
    "answer": "What, don\u2019t you damn millennials know how to read a map? Back in my day we walked uphill to school both ways in the snow!\nAlso, Jacksfilms."
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer what is your favorite video game\n\nVideo games cause violance get the hell off and go play outside",
    "score": 25,
    "author": "doug_da_pug",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nps2y/",
    "question": "What is your favorite video game",
    "answer": "Video games cause violance get the hell off and go play outside"
  },
  {
    "body": "My \"Ok Google\" responses often come back with \"According to Wikipedia...\"\n\nI just imagine every \"Ok Boomer\" starts with \"According to FOX news...\"",
    "score": 24,
    "author": "See_Me_In_A_Crown",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nuize/",
    "question": "My Ok Google responses often come back with According to Wikipedia...",
    "answer": "I just imagine every Ok Boomer starts with According to FOX news..."
  },
  {
    "body": "Man there's like, only negative representations in these replies.. I'ma try something different.\n\n\"Ok Boomer, tell me a story\"\n\n*without missing a beat* \"So let me tell you about this one time the government decided to drop 13 mil on a process to convert corn husk into a viable fuel source and got nothing for it...\"\n\nBoomers have some pretty cool stories",
    "score": 24,
    "author": "snarejunkie",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o10ia/",
    "question": "Man there's like, only negative representations in these replies.. I'ma try something different.",
    "answer": "Ok Boomer, tell me a story\n*without missing a beat* So let me tell you about this one time the government decided to drop 13 mil on a process to convert corn husk into a viable fuel source and got nothing for it...\nBoomers have some pretty cool stories"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, what's the weather outside?\"  \n\"I don't know, open a window.\"",
    "score": 23,
    "author": "zschmeez",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8npxtu/",
    "question": "What's the weather outside?",
    "answer": "I don't know, open a window."
  },
  {
    "body": "Me: \u201cOk Boomer, how do I come out to my parents?\u201d\n\nBoomer: \u201cYou should ask Jesus to forgive you instead!\u201d",
    "score": 23,
    "author": "TheFlutistPotato",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nudxm/",
    "question": "How do i come out to my parents?",
    "answer": "Boomer: You should ask Jesus to forgive you instead!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, remind me to schedule a doctors appointment for this afternoon\u201d\n\n\u201cYou wouldn\u2019t be sick if you weren\u2019t on that damn phone all the time!\u201d",
    "score": 23,
    "author": "blturtle13",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqy78/",
    "question": "Remind me to schedule a doctors appointment for this afternoon",
    "answer": "You wouldn\u2019t be sick if you weren\u2019t on that damn phone all the time!"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok, boomer, how can I be successful?\n\nStay away from those homosexuals. They\u2019re nothing but trouble",
    "score": 23,
    "author": "michelinman112",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nm9p6/",
    "question": "How can i be successful?",
    "answer": "Stay away from those homosexuals. They\u2019re nothing but trouble"
  },
  {
    "body": "Lying out of its ass, but having the confidence to make you think they actually know what they\u2019re talking about.  \n\n\nAlso, slightly racist.",
    "score": 22,
    "author": "skacat",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8np8x8/",
    "question": "Lying out of its ass, but having the confidence to make you think they actually know what they\u2019re talking about.  ",
    "answer": "Also, slightly racist."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok Boomer, how can I pay off my college debt?\"\n\n\"You\u2019re so lazy, I worked my way through college and paid for it myself! Maybe if you didn't pursue that useless art degree, you wouldn\u2019t be in debt!\"",
    "score": 21,
    "author": "dudeihavenoideaa",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nskma/",
    "question": "How can i pay off my college debt?",
    "answer": "You\u2019re so lazy, I worked my way through college and paid for it myself! Maybe if you didn't pursue that useless art degree, you wouldn\u2019t be in debt!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk boomer, I\u2019m pregnant, what do I-\u201c\n\n::device shakes and catches fire while going off the rails with unsolicited, outdated, and abusive advice in a belittling tone::",
    "score": 21,
    "author": "ChaoticAndrea",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o0w4j/",
    "question": "I\u2019m pregnant, what do i-",
    "answer": "::device shakes and catches fire while going off the rails with unsolicited, outdated, and abusive advice in a belittling tone::"
  },
  {
    "body": "I\u2019m 21 lol nice try though. I just fucking hate the term because all it does is cause an even further generalization divide. Ageism is becoming the last accepted form of prejudice. Kind of ironic given how Reddit is so against prejudice in general. Prejudice is making generalizations about a particular group and saying it applies to everyone in that group. How is lumping all baby boomers into the same category not wrong?\n\nEdit: again let the downvotes roll in, but I seriously doubt anyone can refute that. Replace boomer with any other group of people and the pitchforks would be coming out for you.",
    "score": 17,
    "author": "OrangeKlip",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o1jnc/",
    "question": "S into the same category not wrong?",
    "answer": " again let the downvotes roll in, but I seriously doubt anyone can refute that. Replace boomer with any other group of people and the pitchforks would be coming out for you."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk Boomer, where did I park my car?\u201d \n\n\u201cWhere did you see it last?\u201d\n\n...",
    "score": 16,
    "author": "Unit145",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nvan8/",
    "question": "Where did i park my car?",
    "answer": "Where did you see it last?\n..."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, tell me a joke.\"\n\n\"I hate my wife\"",
    "score": 16,
    "author": "Epicat224",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o3mpv/",
    "question": "Tell me a joke.",
    "answer": "I hate my wife"
  },
  {
    "body": "Me: Ok Boomer, start a grocery list.\n\nBoomer: Waaaa?\n\nMe: Start a grocery list.\n\nBoomer: Sorry, I didn\u2019t catch that.\n\nMe: START A GROCERY LIST...\n\nBoomer: Speak up, boy!\n\nMe: START - A - GROCERY - LIST!!!!!\n\nBoomer: .......... Sorry, I need you to speak up.\n\nMe: ........ \n\n\n\n\nFine...... I\u2019ll do it myself....",
    "score": 15,
    "author": "Mortaldeadking",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o3lvc/",
    "question": "Start a grocery list.",
    "answer": "Boomer: Waaaa?\nMe: Start a grocery list.\nBoomer: Sorry, I didn\u2019t catch that.\nMe: START A GROCERY LIST...\nBoomer: Speak up, boy!\nMe: START - A - GROCERY - LIST!!!!!\nBoomer: .......... Sorry, I need you to speak up.\nMe: ........ \nFine...... I\u2019ll do it myself...."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOkay boomer play some traditional Vietnamese music\u201d\n\n*fortunate son begins to play",
    "score": 15,
    "author": "sclinsky26",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o2c92/",
    "question": "Play some traditional vietnamese music",
    "answer": "*fortunate son begins to play"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, look for job listings in my area\"\n\n\"No. Just go speak to the manager of the factory downtown in person. Wear a suit and give him a firm handshake and you'll be set.\"",
    "score": 14,
    "author": "DrCleanly",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nyjmo/",
    "question": "Look for job listings in my area",
    "answer": "No. Just go speak to the manager of the factory downtown in person. Wear a suit and give him a firm handshake and you'll be set."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK Boomer, what will my ballot look like next election?\n\n\"Who cares? Just vote incumbent or whoever you heard about in the advertisements, no one thinks about their votes anyway.\"",
    "score": 14,
    "author": "Pyrrhape",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq79i/",
    "question": "What will my ballot look like next election?",
    "answer": "Who cares? Just vote incumbent or whoever you heard about in the advertisements, no one thinks about their votes anyway."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK Boomer, set a kitchen timer for 8 minutes\u201d\n\n\u201cIsn\u2019t that pasta? You don\u2019t need a timer, it\u2019s done when it sticks to the wall.\u201d",
    "score": 14,
    "author": "KyloWrench",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nnioy/",
    "question": "Set a kitchen timer for 8 minutes",
    "answer": "Isn\u2019t that pasta? You don\u2019t need a timer, it\u2019s done when it sticks to the wall."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Go read a book, ya snowflake.\"\nTo every question.",
    "score": 14,
    "author": "FracturedSublimity16",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nmj8e/",
    "question": "Go read a book, ya snowflake.",
    "answer": "To every question."
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer, how much do you like what I call you?\"\n\n\"Its not nice and it's like saying the n-word.\"\n\n*later randomly says the n-word*",
    "score": 13,
    "author": "GDHeadShot72YT",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8ns79o/",
    "question": "How much do you like what i call you?",
    "answer": "Its not nice and it's like saying the n-word.\n*later randomly says the n-word*"
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOk boomer, how much will i need for a deposit on a house?\u201d\n\n\u201c A paper clip, and stick of gum and some bellybutton lint should suffice.....well it did in my day anyway..\u201d",
    "score": 13,
    "author": "-castle-bravo-",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nos8e/",
    "question": "How much will i need for a deposit on a house?",
    "answer": " A paper clip, and stick of gum and some bellybutton lint should suffice.....well it did in my day anyway.."
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer, where is the nearest Chipotle.\n\n*Go make ur own food*",
    "score": 12,
    "author": "NinjaBoi60000",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nqblf/",
    "question": "Where is the nearest chipotle.",
    "answer": "*Go make ur own food*"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK Boomer.\" Directions to school.\n\n\n\"Walk 5 miles uphill in snow.\"\n\n\n\"But I live in Hawaii.\"",
    "score": 12,
    "author": "lemonhops",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nq1sw/",
    "question": "Directions to school.",
    "answer": "Walk 5 miles uphill in snow.\nBut I live in Hawaii."
  },
  {
    "body": "\u201cOK boomer, what job openings are near me?\u201d\n\n\u201cI\u2019m not going to tell you.  You need to get off the internet, print out 100 copies of your resume, walk door to door in every business park and sell yourself!  I can\u2019t solve your problem, only you can.  So roll up your sleeves get out there, assert yourself and don\u2019t take no for an answer!\u201d",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "Oaken_beard",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nz53p/",
    "question": "What job openings are near me?",
    "answer": "I\u2019m not going to tell you.  You need to get off the internet, print out 100 copies of your resume, walk door to door in every business park and sell yourself!  I can\u2019t solve your problem, only you can.  So roll up your sleeves get out there, assert yourself and don\u2019t take no for an answer!"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"OK boomer, why it there global warming?\"\n\n\"Video games...\"",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "BillOnMyPoopButt69",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8ntrto/",
    "question": "Why it there global warming?",
    "answer": "Video games..."
  },
  {
    "body": "OK, Boomer. How do I tie a tie?\n\n\"I taught you this at your cousin's wedding when you were 6! How the fuck do you not remember?\"",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "KDUFF_Radio",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o5825/",
    "question": "How do i tie a tie?",
    "answer": "I taught you this at your cousin's wedding when you were 6! How the fuck do you not remember?"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Ok boomer play \"welcome to the jungle\" by:guns'N'roses \n\n\"whaAAAAt??\"\n\npLAY \"WELCOME TO THE JUNGLE\"\n\n\"Ya didn't need to shout\"\n*Song plays*\n\nAAAAA THEY'RE IN THE TREES\n*has a heart attack and fucking dies*\n\nHe would also have a voice like Abraham simpson",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "inkybat37",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8npgy1/",
    "question": "Play welcome to the jungle by:guns'n'roses",
    "answer": "whaAAAAt??\npLAY WELCOME TO THE JUNGLE\nYa didn't need to shout\n*Song plays*\nAAAAA THEY'RE IN THE TREES\n*has a heart attack and fucking dies*\nHe would also have a voice like Abraham simpson"
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok Boomer call \"someone\"\n\"No go to their house and actually interact\"",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "creeper_awwman09",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8nryfi/",
    "question": "Call someone",
    "answer": "No go to their house and actually interact"
  },
  {
    "body": "Probably a lot of wisdom, if it had lived a lot of years more than the person who asked.\n\nI remember when I was 20 and some old shit head told me \"you'll see\" and I laughed at his old dumb ass, and now I'm old and I get it and I'm saying it, and being laughed at, and it's just gonna keep going that way forever.\n\nEdit:  Maybe I'll have a midlife crisis and do some spongebob memes and go on tik tok and jesus christ somebody put a bullet though the soft bits in my skull and put me out of my fucking misery.\n\nEdit:  It's rough.  You get a certain age and you feel like you could get in the batting cage or you could run Okies or whatever, but you see Pros who are even younger than you and they've lost it and you realize you can't do it anymore.  Then you think, maybe I'll go the Joe Rogan route and get into Jiu Jitsu and running hills and shit, but then Bourdain did that shit too.  Got in the best shape of his life, trained in BJJ, and he still offed himself.  There's really no light at the end of the fucking tunnel.\n\nEdit:  While I'm ranting.  It's fucking hilarious how people nowadays think everythings so fucking different than it was in the 90s.  Like, people now thing they're saving the Earth, and that nobody gave a shit back then.  But it's the same shit.  Like right now people are frowning on plastic straws, as if that shit makes a difference in the big scheme of things.  With the scale of industrial pollution and production of useless plastic bullshit.  That all goes in landfills.  In the 90's it was CFCs.  Stop using aerosols, like hairspray.  So people would stop using hairspray as if it put a fucking dent in the amount of CFCs that were being produced by world industry.  People just wanna feel good, as if they're helping.  No plastic straws, cut up your 6 pack plastic rings, don't use aerosol cans.  Meanwhile China's pumping more shit in the air and producing more plastic bullshit than you could possibly use in a million lifetimes.  \n\nI'm gonna keep ranting, fuck you.\n\nA while back I saw two things in one day on reddit that made me want to gouge my fucking eyes out and shove them up my ass.\n\nOne was a comic.  This webcomic creator, who usually does funny stuff, did one where she talked about losing a family member to cancer.  In the comic she drew herself standing on a cliff/bluff at sunset, and she said some heartfelt stuff and released a balloon into the setting sun.  Like, she said \"even though you're gone, you'll always be with me.\"  Then she released the baloon into the sunset.  As a way of letting go.\n\nWanna know what one of the top comments was?\n\n\"Oh nice, litter.\"\n\nIt was a fucking comic.  A drawing.  And even then, it was a single balloon.  Do these people have any idea what the sheer scale of human pollution is?\n\nI'll answer that for you, because right after I saw that, I saw another one.\n\nSomeone posted a gif of someone putting a couple of drops of pen ink onto a leaf, then they put the leaf into a puddle.  Somehow the ink propelled the leaf around the puddle, like a little motorboat.\n\nPretty cool right?\n\nNope.\n\nSomebody bitched about pollution.  From a few drops of pen ink.  That's non-toxic btw.  But like 3 drops of ink, either way.  And it had like 40 upvotes.\n\nDo these people have any fucking idea of the scale of shit?  How fucking stupid are they?  \n\nDrops of pen ink.  It's not even toxic.  Non toxic pen ink.  Three drops.  Not even \"a drop in a bucket.\"  A drop in the entire world's aquifer.\n\nFucking hell.\n\nStop being \"woke\" and splash some water on your face and wake the fuck up.  Get some fucking sense.\n\nThis is too long to be a copypasta you cunts.\n\nEdit:  Man, I had a lot to drink.  You can still go fuck yourselves though.",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "sterling_mallory",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o7fg8/",
    "question": "Probably a lot of wisdom, if it had lived a lot of years more than the person who asked.",
    "answer": "  Maybe I'll have a midlife crisis and do some spongebob memes and go on tik tok and jesus christ somebody put a bullet though the soft bits in my skull and put me out of my fucking misery.\nEdit:  It's rough.  You get a certain age and you feel like you could get in the batting cage or you could run Okies or whatever, but you see Pros who are even younger than you and they've lost it and you realize you can't do it anymore.  Then you think, maybe I'll go the Joe Rogan route and get into Jiu Jitsu and running hills and shit, but then Bourdain did that shit too.  Got in the best shape of his life, trained in BJJ, and he still offed himself.  There's really no light at the end of the fucking tunnel.\nEdit:  While I'm ranting.  It's fucking hilarious how people nowadays think everythings so fucking different than it was in the 90s.  Like, people now thing they're saving the Earth, and that nobody gave a shit back then.  But it's the same shit.  Like right now people are frowning on plastic straws, as if that shit makes a difference in the big scheme of things.  With the scale of industrial pollution and production of useless plastic bullshit.  That all goes in landfills.  In the 90's it was CFCs.  Stop using aerosols, like hairspray.  So people would stop using hairspray as if it put a fucking dent in the amount of CFCs that were being produced by world industry.  People just wanna feel good, as if they're helping.  No plastic straws, cut up your 6 pack plastic rings, don't use aerosol cans.  Meanwhile China's pumping more shit in the air and producing more plastic bullshit than you could possibly use in a million lifetimes.  \nI'm gonna keep ranting, fuck you.\nA while back I saw two things in one day on reddit that made me want to gouge my fucking eyes out and shove them up my ass.\nOne was a comic.  This webcomic creator, who usually does funny stuff, did one where she talked about losing a family member to cancer.  In the comic she drew herself standing on a cliff/bluff at sunset, and she said some heartfelt stuff and released a balloon into the setting sun.  Like, she said even though you're gone, you'll always be with me.  Then she released the baloon into the sunset.  As a way of letting go.\nWanna know what one of the top comments was?\nOh nice, litter.\nIt was a fucking comic.  A drawing.  And even then, it was a single balloon.  Do these people have any idea what the sheer scale of human pollution is?\nI'll answer that for you, because right after I saw that, I saw another one.\nSomeone posted a gif of someone putting a couple of drops of pen ink onto a leaf, then they put the leaf into a puddle.  Somehow the ink propelled the leaf around the puddle, like a little motorboat.\nPretty cool right?\nNope.\nSomebody bitched about pollution.  From a few drops of pen ink.  That's non-toxic btw.  But like 3 drops of ink, either way.  And it had like 40 upvotes.\nDo these people have any fucking idea of the scale of shit?  How fucking stupid are they?  \nDrops of pen ink.  It's not even toxic.  Non toxic pen ink.  Three drops.  Not even a drop in a bucket.  A drop in the entire world's aquifer.\nFucking hell.\nStop being woke and splash some water on your face and wake the fuck up.  Get some fucking sense.\nThis is too long to be a copypasta you cunts.\nEdit:  Man, I had a lot to drink.  You can still go fuck yourselves though."
  },
  {
    "body": "Ok boomer, how do I avoid scams\n\nBoomer: dont pick up spam calls now shut up and let me talk to this Nigerian prince",
    "score": 11,
    "author": "Kanye4prezedent2020",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8noitu/",
    "question": "How do i avoid scams",
    "answer": "Boomer: dont pick up spam calls now shut up and let me talk to this Nigerian prince"
  },
  {
    "body": "\"Okay Boomer, where is the nearest health clinic?\"\n\n\"I'll send you my thoughts and prayers.\"",
    "score": 10,
    "author": "SoothsayerAtlas",
    "permalink": "/r/AskReddit/comments/e18g6m/if_ok_boomer_was_a_digital_assistant_like_ok/f8o4w0f/",
    "question": "Where is the nearest health clinic?",
    "answer": "I'll send you my thoughts and prayers."
  }
]
